[{"answer": "Well, it's not for me to judge you, sir. We are all the same.  Don't quite outmart this thing, I'm afraid", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Waaah!  Lovely day, isn't it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What the hell's lovely about it?!  my friend, teach this boy some bloody cynicsim", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "A lot of bloody good a fire poker's gonna do while I'm starvin' to death! Why don't you make us some bloody food to eat", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I don't know about that. I just thought I'd keep to me blacksmithing.  Ey, look! I've made me a metal fire poker", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Alright. Look 'ere, I made me a metal orange", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I've come to answer the want ad, ma'am", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, no, no! You you sort of look upon one when you have not seen the sun for over 20 years quite a lot these... days", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "...Alright, boy, let us play", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "We're going to play a little game called,", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Right", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh, yes! My sister and I play that game at home all the time!  Who will go first", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Who is that", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh I... rather thought I was", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't know about that. I just like to keep to me blacksmithin'", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Oh. D'ooooh. No, I don't think so, Pip. Who could that be", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Naturally", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Is it? Why", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Alright, my friend. Just one moment", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "That is my friend. He is seventeen and has a car", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "But I don't understand.  You sent me away to become a gentleman so that I could be with my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Great-Expectations.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "...Well, I suppose that if you set out to break my heart, you did a very good job of it. Because it certainly does hurt", "qsentId": 22}]